hyperwebenable.com 2012-09-20

# hyperwebenable.com Privacy Policy

We here at Hyperwebenable.com take your privacy very seriously. We strive to ensure that your private information remains private. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the Hyperwebenable.com web site collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of this Web Site.

**I. Privacy**  
Hyperwebenable.com provides many different services to it's visitors, members, and customers. This policy states the company-wide Privacy Policy with regard to data collection practices.

By visiting Hyperwebenable.com, becoming a registered member or customer of any service, or participating in promotions, contests, etc. you hereby provide your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy, and are aware that our policy may change over time as discussed below. Specifically, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect new features, services and options, and any changes on the use of personal information. Continued use of Hyperwebenable.com Services will indicate that you agree with any changes.

**II. Nature of Information Collected**   
There are two types of information collected by Hyperwebenable.com: (A) anonymous and (B) personally identifiable information. The Hyperwebenable.com Network's collection practices regarding these two are discussed in greater detail below.

A. Anonymous Information Collection   
Anonymous information refers to information that cannot be tied back to a specific individual. As with visiting any web site, Hyperwebenable.com collects some basic information about your computer, including browser type, operating system, IP address, Internet service provider and geographic location.

B. Personally Identifiable Information   
Personally identifiable information can be used to directly identify an individual. Hyperwebenable.com requires personal information to be collected in order to create your account. 

**III. Use of Cookies**   
Hyperwebenable.com uses cookies throughout our web sites. A cookie is simply a small data file sent to your computer that identifies your computer to a specific web site. It also collects anonymous information and tracks traffic patterns. A cookie will not provide any personally identifiable information about you, nor will it read data off of your hard drive, or read cookie files created by other web sites. Hyperwebenable.com uses the information provided by a cookie for tracking site usage and targeting of advertising. This allows Hyperwebenable.com to customize your visit and save you time during subsequent visits. 

**IV. Purposes for Which Information is Collected**  
Hyperwebenable.com tracks anonymous information to determine which pages are preferred based on traffic to those areas and provide marketing information to our advertisers and sponsors. This information is aggregated to provide Hyperwebenable.com with demographic and other statistical data that allows us to assess how well our web site is performing. 

The personal information collected from our members and customers, or anyone that submits their personal information, is used to create and maintain the services requested. This includes corresponding with our members and customers by e-mail, postal mail, or phone. This correspondence is for the purpose of keeping our members and customers up to date with important system announcements and updates, and also for offering relevant third party opportunities via email. Unsubscribe procedures from non-account maintenance notifications are posted at the bottom of each email.

**V. Sharing of Information Collected by Hyperwebenable.com**   
Hyperwebenable.com only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Hyperwebenable.com in the following limited circumstances:We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 

We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.   
We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Hyperwebenable.com , its users or the public as required or permitted by law.   
If Hyperwebenable.com becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. 

**VI. Links to Third Parties**   
Hyperwebenable.com's web sites contain links to other web sites. When accessing the web sites of third parties, including through ad banners and other links, you will be accessing sites that are not operated or controlled by Hyperwebenable.com. These sites may collect anonymous and personal information by various methods, including the use of cookies. The privacy policies of these web sites may not be the same as those of Hyperwebenable.com and may not afford visitors and citizens the same level of protection. Visitors and citizens should contact these advertisers to verify the privacy policies of these web sites and their terms of use when accessing them and prior to providing any anonymous or personal information.

**VII. Storage and Security**  
We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. We restrict access to personal information to employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**VIII. Review and Correction of Information**   
Customers and Members who have submitted personal information may, at any time, review the information relating to them contained in Hyperwebenable.com databases and edit any incorrect information. To review the information follow the instructions provided within your account. 

**IX. Protection of Minors**   
The protection of children's online privacy is very important to The Hyperwebenable.com Network. For that reason, it is our policy not to collect or maintain information at our web sites from those we actually know are under 13 and no part of our web sites is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**X. Consent, Opt-In and Opt-Out**  
Visitors and members of The Hyperwebenable.com Network confirm by visiting any of the sites or the submission of their personal information that they consent to the collection and processing of personal information, the use of cookies and transfer of personal data in countries other than their country of residence.

**XI.POLICY UPDATES**  
We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes).
